<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Freedom on (soon to be) riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/tags/freedom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Freedom on (soon to be) riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rmdegennaro.github.io/tags/freedom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Find, Bandcamp.com!</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2011/03/19/bandcamp-more-then-music-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2011/03/19/bandcamp-more-then-music-store/</guid>
      <description>Surfing can be fun. I am usually targeted in my use of the Internet, but I&amp;rsquo;m really glad I found this website.
It started out from a potentially annoying thing. Someone whom I have no relation, nor do I have any idea why they wanted to &amp;ldquo;be my friend&amp;rdquo; on Last.fm. That site isn&amp;rsquo;t the website of interest, and I love Last.fm to get recommendations on music. Anyways, I found out it was a band that was being &amp;ldquo;sly&amp;rdquo; as also being a &amp;ldquo;user&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The “Ground Zero Mosque” Debate Makes No Sense</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/08/21/ground-zero-mosque-debate-makes-no-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/08/21/ground-zero-mosque-debate-makes-no-sense/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start posting links to articles I like. Word of mouth and discussing things among friends is what helps make the world more cohesive and ultimately a better place. It also helps lessen fear and increases strength within and without.
So my first is this article: 3 Reasons the “Ground Zero Mosque” Debate Makes No Sense
A highlight is that rhetoric should never replace logic. Our lives are not controlled by fear, and fear spreads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Election Results, 2009</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/01/20/election-results-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/01/20/election-results-2009/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while. And this one isn&amp;rsquo;t really mine. But, like many, for the first time in a long time, I look to the future with a promising smile. Thanks to Jen, Jim and Ken for their wonderful words.
Barak Obama! Freakylicious President! Get your &amp;ldquo;Mo Jo&amp;rdquo; on! A Haiku from Jen Jag
In bare feet by the thousands, chain-yanked off the auction block, In pinched shoes moving on northward flight, In just bought boots down the new hallways of Tuskegee, In spikes churning up the Berlin dirt under the Fuhrer’s eye, In laced-high shoes stepping through the ring to meet Schmeling In ankle high russet browns trudging through the mud of Anzio and stumbling over the crushed rock of Okinawa, In flashing feet breaking for home plate and all of Brooklyn’s approving roar, In the patent leather shoes of three little girls taking guarded steps to school, In wild gliding, unstoppable, sliding motion on the floor of the Apollo, In steel-toed GPs scrambling for cover at Tet and slogging the water-logged Mekong, In stride, linked and determined, on the march, a preacher’s shined shoes at the fore, from Selma to Montgomery, Albany, Birmingham, Chicago, and up the steps to dream in Lincoln’s shadow, that long shadow cast across the generations, across the throngs of Washington Mall who have been on the move from every corner of the country and pause now in wonder at where the weary feet have led.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Like the G1 Android phone by T-Mobile?</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve held back on commenting about the G1 from T-Mobile. Mostly for technical reasons and time-wise reasons. But also because I&amp;rsquo;ve been uncertain about how it will turn out and how to talk about it (mostly to non-techie people). Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve had high hopes for it and the Andriod platform. And to say my hopes have been met is not an easy thing.
First, for the non-techies, the G1 is the phone, T-Mobile the carrier and Andriod is the OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>