<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foss on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/foss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foss on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 15:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ChromiumOS on my XPS M1530 (and other computers)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been itching to see how a ChromeOS device works. I want to see how well a ChromeBook would fill the home computing needs. Since I have this nice Dell Latitude XPS M1530, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d do some research to see if I could run ChromeOS on it.
There is a person, Hexxeh, who provides nightly builds of the open source ChromiumOS project. These can be downloaded as bootable USB flash drive image, VMWare or VirtualBox disk images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Low-resource Linux for a Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2010/05/12/simple-low-resource-linux-virtual-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2010/05/12/simple-low-resource-linux-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I work remotely in almost everything I do for work. I.e. I remote into the servers and workstations all day every day; very little gets done on my laptop except personal stuff. Whether it be development, database manipulation, webapp/system management, or regular&amp;rsquo;ol&amp;rsquo;tech-support. The projects are mostly for clients, so they stay on clients machines, but I do have my own servers.
Also, most clients use routers (or whatever does the DHCP) out of the box at their office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Like the G1 Android phone by T-Mobile?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve held back on commenting about the G1 from T-Mobile. Mostly for technical reasons and time-wise reasons. But also because I&amp;rsquo;ve been uncertain about how it will turn out and how to talk about it (mostly to non-techie people). Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve had high hopes for it and the Andriod platform. And to say my hopes have been met is not an easy thing.
First, for the non-techies, the G1 is the phone, T-Mobile the carrier and Andriod is the OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>