<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 19:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An IBM T42 with Manjaro</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/13/ibm-t42-with-manjaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/13/ibm-t42-with-manjaro/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve taken quite a liking to Manjaro. All the random tasks I&amp;rsquo;ve used it for have turned out extremely well. Enough so that I want to go beyond those very directed needs and do a general review. And I&amp;rsquo;ll start out by installing Manjaro on my IBM/Lenovo T42.
Which is a little late since they just announced deprecating 32-bit / i686 support. So, since I did all this work over a few months, I figure I might as well put out this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaro, a distro that I&#39;m really digging</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/04/02/manjaro-a-distro-im-really-diggin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/04/02/manjaro-a-distro-im-really-diggin/</guid>
      <description>Linux &amp;ldquo;distros&amp;rdquo; are many. Linux is awesome that way: scratch an itch, climb that mountain, being as satisfied as a cat. I encourage folks to explore. Head over to Distro Watch to start exploring.
But what makes one stick to a distro? Its a very personal thing. This is the Internet, so I&amp;rsquo;m shouting out what&amp;rsquo;s important to me. :-) A bit of history first. I started in 1997 with Red Hat, moved to Gentoo to learn nuts and bolts, then ended up using Kubuntu because I liked things &amp;ldquo;that just worked&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing on a Chromebook (well, CloudReady), Part 1</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/11/28/developing-on-a-chromebook-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/11/28/developing-on-a-chromebook-part1/</guid>
      <description>I like the idea of Chrome Apps. It is (was?) a great idea; write one app and it will run on Linux, Chrome OS, Mac and Windows (yeah, the order is telling). It&amp;rsquo;s a shame Google has announced it will stop supporting Chrome Apps on Linux, Mac and Windows. So initially this started out as a log of my adventure of making a Chrome App on Chrome OS (well a Chromium OS distro called CloudReady).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>antergos, Arch made simple</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/15/antergos-arch-made-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/15/antergos-arch-made-simple/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, back at my distro hopping. Well, not really, the main machines (desktop and laptop) are still Kubuntu. But if there were a distro to switch to, it might be antergos Linux. At least at first &amp;ldquo;blush&amp;rdquo;. Wow, easy install, easy setup, easy updates. And it feels snappy&amp;hellip;
More details to come. For now, the machine is a Toshiba Satellite A105-S4254: Intel Dual Core T2050 / 1.6 GHz, 3GB RAM, 7200RPM SATA hard drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using CloudReady, A Linux/Chromium OS Distro - Part 2 (12/04/2015)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/04/using-cloudready-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/04/using-cloudready-part2/</guid>
      <description>This is getting to be really late. I forgot to post it, and have since moved on to testing Antergos Linux. Anyways, here is an &amp;ldquo;almost too old to post to post&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using CloudReady on an off on this laptop for a while now. Everything works pretty swimmingly. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the whole Google ecosystem, then using CloudReady should be pretty seamless.
I&amp;rsquo;ve seen many reviews with agendas, either their own or someone else&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using CloudReady, A Linux/Chromium OS Distro - Part 1 (11/8/2015)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/11/08/using-cloudready-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/11/08/using-cloudready-part1/</guid>
      <description>Back to blogging a bit because I&amp;rsquo;m recovering from some surgery. Nothing major. Its only been almost a year and half since my last blogging. :-)
So last time I blogged I used my Toshiba Satellite A105-S4254 laptop to test out Android-x86. A fun experiment, and proved to myself that Android can be used as a desktop if you don&amp;rsquo;t need sophisticated content creation.
Since then I used this laptop to create my own &amp;ldquo;DIY Chromebook&amp;rdquo; using Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part VI (8/15/2014 - 8/22/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/22/test-drive-android-x86-part6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 23:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/22/test-drive-android-x86-part6/</guid>
      <description>Finishing up my chronicling of using an old laptop that is now running Android-x86. It was running Windows XP. And I hate to throw away useful hardware, but also don&amp;rsquo;t want to use an out-of-date insecure operating system.
Where we last left off was a bit of a hiccup in things. Nothing major, but things were unstable when I had two Google accounts configured at the same time. After I removed the extra account, things have been running smoothly for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part V (8/13/2014 - 8/14/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/14/test-drive-android-x86-part5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/14/test-drive-android-x86-part5/</guid>
      <description>Most of my posts on the topic of running Android-x86 on my old former Windows XP laptop have been positive. And I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m still positive in general.
Some bad news though is that a bunch of updates for Apps came down and now things are blowing up when I have more then one Google account setup. It took some efforts in trouble shooting and a few reloads in various ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part IV (8/10/2014 - 8/12/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/12/test-drive-android-x86-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/12/test-drive-android-x86-part4/</guid>
      <description>Okay, a busy weekend, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do much. Sunday was disc (ultimate frisbee-ish), and a bit of work. So no time to do anything on this Android-x86 laptop.
And yesterday, Monday, all I really had time to do was update to Android-x86&amp;rsquo;s first 4.4 release. There isn&amp;rsquo;t any OTA updates, but you can still download the ISO, boot to it, and perform an upgrade just like OTA update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part III (8/9/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/09/test-drive-android-x86-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/09/test-drive-android-x86-part3/</guid>
      <description>So its Saturday. I&amp;rsquo;d thought I&amp;rsquo;d have time to do some additional work related stuff and play on my Android-x86 laptop. But alas, because of errands and usual Saturday shtiff, not much time to play. But I did do some stuff:
 Work had power outage, so was emailing and IM&amp;rsquo;ing on the Android laptop. Also had to look up some stuff to IM my tech support guy who went on site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part II (over a few days)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/08/test-drive-android-x86-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/08/test-drive-android-x86-part2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been really busy, so haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to keep track of the little I did well. This is basically chronicling my experiment of using Android-x86 on a laptop that used to run Windows XP. Here is a recap of a couple of days combined.
8/5/2014  Checked email, easy to do when brain-dead from a long day. Played Andor&amp;rsquo;s Trail a little bit. Noticed the cut and paste semantics feel a bit odd, but that&amp;rsquo;s because keyboard shortcuts are not available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part I (8/4/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/04/test-drive-android-x86-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/04/test-drive-android-x86-part1/</guid>
      <description>I have an old Toshiba 32-Bit laptop that had Windows XP on it. And since Windows XP is no longer supported, I decided to put Android-x86 on it. I did this a while back, but haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to play with it much. My plan now is to use it as my main laptop and keep a log of what I do or can&amp;rsquo;t do on it for the next bit&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChromiumOS on my XPS M1530 (and other computers)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been itching to see how a ChromeOS device works. I want to see how well a ChromeBook would fill the home computing needs. Since I have this nice Dell Latitude XPS M1530, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d do some research to see if I could run ChromeOS on it.
There is a person, Hexxeh, who provides nightly builds of the open source ChromiumOS project. These can be downloaded as bootable USB flash drive image, VMWare or VirtualBox disk images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New system. New blog entry. New distro too?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/19/new-system-new-blog-entry-new-distro-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/19/new-system-new-blog-entry-new-distro-too/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the opportunity to get an Dell XPS M1530 really cheap. So we have the home laptop and now I have a laptop to play around with. Yah!
My intention is to blog what I do with the XPS laptop. As I have time to play with it, I&amp;rsquo;ll add new blog entries. Changing jobs and home life causing changes in focus is okay too. Right now I&amp;rsquo;ve loaded Linux Mint Debian Edition, with the Cinnamon desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kid3 Kicks, ah, Well It&#39;s A Kyamo Replacement</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2011/07/26/kid3-kick-ah-well-its-a-kyamo-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 01:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2011/07/26/kid3-kick-ah-well-its-a-kyamo-replacement/</guid>
      <description>So for ages I&amp;rsquo;ve used Kyamo to edit MP3 tags. It had been great because it edited multiple tag versions and it also not only viewed embedded album art, but allowed you to edit it. Sadly Kyamo is no longer supported in K/Ubuntu. Well, as with most FOSS, you can always grab the source and compile it yourself.
I had wished I had time to do just that, and maybe update/maintain it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Low-resource Linux for a Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2010/05/12/simple-low-resource-linux-virtual-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2010/05/12/simple-low-resource-linux-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I work remotely in almost everything I do for work. I.e. I remote into the servers and workstations all day every day; very little gets done on my laptop except personal stuff. Whether it be development, database manipulation, webapp/system management, or regular&amp;rsquo;ol&amp;rsquo;tech-support. The projects are mostly for clients, so they stay on clients machines, but I do have my own servers.
Also, most clients use routers (or whatever does the DHCP) out of the box at their office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Like the G1 Android phone by T-Mobile?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve held back on commenting about the G1 from T-Mobile. Mostly for technical reasons and time-wise reasons. But also because I&amp;rsquo;ve been uncertain about how it will turn out and how to talk about it (mostly to non-techie people). Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve had high hopes for it and the Andriod platform. And to say my hopes have been met is not an easy thing.
First, for the non-techies, the G1 is the phone, T-Mobile the carrier and Andriod is the OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>