<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hardware on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/hardware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hardware on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 21:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Modding a NuVision TM800W560L Tablet</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/24/modding-a-nuvision-tm800w560l-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/24/modding-a-nuvision-tm800w560l-tablet/</guid>
      <description>So a friend gave me a NuVision tm800w560l tablet running Windows 10. Honestly I tried to use it, but it was a joke. From the start with it not connecting to WiFi because Windows 10 wanted uppercase alpha characters even though every other Linux, Android, Mac OS X or iOS device works with lower case. To the fact that the on screen keyboard would hide where I was typing. To the periodic hick-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An IBM T42 with Manjaro</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/13/ibm-t42-with-manjaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2017/09/13/ibm-t42-with-manjaro/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve taken quite a liking to Manjaro. All the random tasks I&amp;rsquo;ve used it for have turned out extremely well. Enough so that I want to go beyond those very directed needs and do a general review. And I&amp;rsquo;ll start out by installing Manjaro on my IBM/Lenovo T42.
Which is a little late since they just announced deprecating 32-bit / i686 support. So, since I did all this work over a few months, I figure I might as well put out this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using A Remix Mini PC</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/12/17/using-a-remix-mini-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/12/17/using-a-remix-mini-pc/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m late to the game on the Remix Mini PC; which is basically a phone that a monitor, keyboard and mouse get plugged into. [edit] I&amp;rsquo;ve also updated this blog post. One reason is I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it exclusively in the living room. Also, Jide announced they are exiting the consumer market. [/edit] I bought one a bit back because it was on sale and I figured why not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing on a Chromebook (well, CloudReady), Part 1</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/11/28/developing-on-a-chromebook-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/11/28/developing-on-a-chromebook-part1/</guid>
      <description>I like the idea of Chrome Apps. It is (was?) a great idea; write one app and it will run on Linux, Chrome OS, Mac and Windows (yeah, the order is telling). It&amp;rsquo;s a shame Google has announced it will stop supporting Chrome Apps on Linux, Mac and Windows. So initially this started out as a log of my adventure of making a Chrome App on Chrome OS (well a Chromium OS distro called CloudReady).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New system. New blog entry. New distro too?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/19/new-system-new-blog-entry-new-distro-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/19/new-system-new-blog-entry-new-distro-too/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the opportunity to get an Dell XPS M1530 really cheap. So we have the home laptop and now I have a laptop to play around with. Yah!
My intention is to blog what I do with the XPS laptop. As I have time to play with it, I&amp;rsquo;ll add new blog entries. Changing jobs and home life causing changes in focus is okay too. Right now I&amp;rsquo;ve loaded Linux Mint Debian Edition, with the Cinnamon desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Like the G1 Android phone by T-Mobile?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve held back on commenting about the G1 from T-Mobile. Mostly for technical reasons and time-wise reasons. But also because I&amp;rsquo;ve been uncertain about how it will turn out and how to talk about it (mostly to non-techie people). Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve had high hopes for it and the Andriod platform. And to say my hopes have been met is not an easy thing.
First, for the non-techies, the G1 is the phone, T-Mobile the carrier and Andriod is the OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>