<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/categories/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/categories/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This is a family recipe, not sure how long, but I got it from my mom.
Ingredients:  3 bananas, mashed 3 eggs, beaten slightly 1 cup sugar OR 2&amp;frasl;3 cup honey 2 cups flour 1&amp;frasl;4 cup soy flour 2 tbsp wheat germ 2 tbsp brewer&amp;rsquo;s yeast 2 tsp. baking powder 1 tsp baking soda 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp salt 1 tsp vanilla 2&amp;frasl;3 cup oil 2&amp;frasl;3 cup orange juice  Instructions: Preheat oven to 350 degrees, mix all ingredients together, bake in 10&amp;rdquo; tube pan for ~55 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Korma</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/chicken-korma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/chicken-korma/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This recipe started with me trying to figure out how something was made at a restaurant. It&amp;rsquo;s evolved over time where I&amp;rsquo;ve tweaked things as I felt necessary.
Ingredients:  2 lbs. chicken breasts &amp;amp; thighs (boneless, skinless) 2 cups yogurt (I like firm greek yogurt) 2 tbs butter 1 green chillies (diced) 4 garlic cloves (crushed) whole peppercorns whole cloves whole cardamom seeds cumin tumeric black pepper saffron  Instructions: Cook cloves, peppercorns &amp;amp; cardamom seeds in oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeGennaro Tomato Sauce</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/degennaro-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/degennaro-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This is mostly off the top of my head. I&amp;rsquo;ve tweaked this as I&amp;rsquo;ve made it and remembered to edit it. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry that when I make it I don&amp;rsquo;t really think, I just go. It is based on a family recipe passed down. I.e. mostly traditional, but varied over the generations. So this is the basic idea, I&amp;rsquo;ll do more for &amp;ldquo;insight&amp;rdquo; into a good sauce at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot &amp; Sweet Shrimp</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/hot-sweet-shrimp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/hot-sweet-shrimp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: I copied this down from a package. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to tweak it to my pleasure with real spices/ingredients, not what is included in the pre-fab package.
Ingredients:  1 lbs. shrimp (shelled) 2 onions (diced) 4 tomatoes (diced) 2 tbs tomato puree 4 garlic cloves (crushed) 3 green chillies (diced) 2 tbs sugar (raw best) couple dashes coriander couple dashes cumin couple dashes tumeric couple dashes red chili powder couple dashes amchoor (mango powder) couple dashes garam masala  Instructions: Fry onions with oil until golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories of Madras Curry</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/memories-of-madras-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2000/01/01/memories-of-madras-curry/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This is just from some scribbled notes from something I&amp;rsquo;ve done on-the-fly.
Ingredients:  2 lbs. chicken breasts &amp;amp; thighs (boneless, skinless) 4 onions (diced) 4 tomatoes (diced) 3 green chillies (diced) 2 tbls ginger (freshly chopped/shaved) 4 garlic cloves (crushed) nutmeg whole cloves cardamom seeds couple dashes coriander couple dashes cumin couple dashes tumeric  Instructions: Grind cloves &amp;amp; cardamom in mortal &amp;amp; pestle. Heat some oil and cook clove &amp;amp; cardamom for a tiny bit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>