<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Android on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/android/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Android on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 18:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using A Remix Mini PC</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/12/17/using-a-remix-mini-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2016/12/17/using-a-remix-mini-pc/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m late to the game on the Remix Mini PC; which is basically a phone that a monitor, keyboard and mouse get plugged into. [edit] I&amp;rsquo;ve also updated this blog post. One reason is I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it exclusively in the living room. Also, Jide announced they are exiting the consumer market. [/edit] I bought one a bit back because it was on sale and I figured why not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part VI (8/15/2014 - 8/22/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/22/test-drive-android-x86-part6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 23:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/22/test-drive-android-x86-part6/</guid>
      <description>Finishing up my chronicling of using an old laptop that is now running Android-x86. It was running Windows XP. And I hate to throw away useful hardware, but also don&amp;rsquo;t want to use an out-of-date insecure operating system.
Where we last left off was a bit of a hiccup in things. Nothing major, but things were unstable when I had two Google accounts configured at the same time. After I removed the extra account, things have been running smoothly for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part V (8/13/2014 - 8/14/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/14/test-drive-android-x86-part5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/14/test-drive-android-x86-part5/</guid>
      <description>Most of my posts on the topic of running Android-x86 on my old former Windows XP laptop have been positive. And I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m still positive in general.
Some bad news though is that a bunch of updates for Apps came down and now things are blowing up when I have more then one Google account setup. It took some efforts in trouble shooting and a few reloads in various ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part IV (8/10/2014 - 8/12/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/12/test-drive-android-x86-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/12/test-drive-android-x86-part4/</guid>
      <description>Okay, a busy weekend, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do much. Sunday was disc (ultimate frisbee-ish), and a bit of work. So no time to do anything on this Android-x86 laptop.
And yesterday, Monday, all I really had time to do was update to Android-x86&amp;rsquo;s first 4.4 release. There isn&amp;rsquo;t any OTA updates, but you can still download the ISO, boot to it, and perform an upgrade just like OTA update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part III (8/9/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/09/test-drive-android-x86-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/09/test-drive-android-x86-part3/</guid>
      <description>So its Saturday. I&amp;rsquo;d thought I&amp;rsquo;d have time to do some additional work related stuff and play on my Android-x86 laptop. But alas, because of errands and usual Saturday shtiff, not much time to play. But I did do some stuff:
 Work had power outage, so was emailing and IM&amp;rsquo;ing on the Android laptop. Also had to look up some stuff to IM my tech support guy who went on site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part II (over a few days)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/08/test-drive-android-x86-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/08/test-drive-android-x86-part2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been really busy, so haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to keep track of the little I did well. This is basically chronicling my experiment of using Android-x86 on a laptop that used to run Windows XP. Here is a recap of a couple of days combined.
8/5/2014  Checked email, easy to do when brain-dead from a long day. Played Andor&amp;rsquo;s Trail a little bit. Noticed the cut and paste semantics feel a bit odd, but that&amp;rsquo;s because keyboard shortcuts are not available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x86, Part I (8/4/2014)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/04/test-drive-android-x86-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2014/08/04/test-drive-android-x86-part1/</guid>
      <description>I have an old Toshiba 32-Bit laptop that had Windows XP on it. And since Windows XP is no longer supported, I decided to put Android-x86 on it. I did this a while back, but haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to play with it much. My plan now is to use it as my main laptop and keep a log of what I do or can&amp;rsquo;t do on it for the next bit&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Like the G1 Android phone by T-Mobile?</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/12/09/andriod-g1-by-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve held back on commenting about the G1 from T-Mobile. Mostly for technical reasons and time-wise reasons. But also because I&amp;rsquo;ve been uncertain about how it will turn out and how to talk about it (mostly to non-techie people). Also, I&amp;rsquo;ve had high hopes for it and the Andriod platform. And to say my hopes have been met is not an easy thing.
First, for the non-techies, the G1 is the phone, T-Mobile the carrier and Andriod is the OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>