<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>(soon to be) riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on (soon to be) riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 19:18:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Use of Hugo</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/blog/2017/10/14/my-first-use-of-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 19:18:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/blog/2017/10/14/my-first-use-of-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I make myself laugh. The title is so &amp;ldquo;meta&amp;rdquo;. My first use of hugo is in hugo. :-/
Anyways, for the most part, so far, so good for the most past. I&amp;rsquo;ve created a site, added some themes and created this first post. There are some hiccups along the way though. They are all documentation related at this point.
Little Bumps In The Road First one, is a chicken and the egg sort of thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeGennaro Tomato Sauce</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/blog/2000/01/01/degennaro-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/blog/2000/01/01/degennaro-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This is mostly off the top of my head. I&amp;rsquo;ve tweaked this as I&amp;rsquo;ve made it and remembered to edit it. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry that when I make it I don&amp;rsquo;t really think, I just go. It is based on a family recipe passed down. I.e. mostly traditional, but varied over the generations. So this is the basic idea, I&amp;rsquo;ll do more for &amp;ldquo;insight&amp;rdquo; into a good sauce at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food &amp; Recipes</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/food/</guid>
      <description>I love food. I like to eat, I like to cook. I&amp;rsquo;m part Italian and a cancer; what can I say? I also like to make up my own recipes, usually only reading cook books for ideas.
Recipes are very limited right now, as I have recipes, like so much else, scattered in books, files, websites, bookmarks, scraps of paper, etc. With the new Google Sites there is not an automatic way to create a list of sub-pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/music/</guid>
      <description>Music is a big part of my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve been in a few bands through out my history, check that info out below. My tastes are varied and since I&amp;rsquo;ve started using Google Play Music to listen to and sync music across devices, I don&amp;rsquo;t really have something to share for my tastes. You could check out my last.fm page, but it is probably out of date by quite a number of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/gohugo_site/resume/</guid>
      <description>rmdegennaro@gmail.com, (www.linkedin.com/in/rmdegennaro)
SUMMARY Collaborative, practical, results-oriented Director Of Technology driven to guide organizations in incorporating seasoned technology. Adept identifying needs and connecting to innovative and intuitive solutions. Excels at building productive and strategic relationships and effective teams while maintaining an eye on costs and an organization’s direction.
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY South Shore Charter Public School - Director of Technology &amp;amp; Communication (2011 – Present)  School Leadership: Collaborate with school leaders &amp;amp; teachers to determine technology systems to meet school policy, procedural and financial requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>