<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chromeos on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/chromeos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chromeos on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 08:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/chromeos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using CloudReady, A Linux/Chromium OS Distro - Part 2 (12/04/2015)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/04/using-cloudready-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/12/04/using-cloudready-part2/</guid>
      <description>This is getting to be really late. I forgot to post it, and have since moved on to testing Antergos Linux. Anyways, here is an &amp;ldquo;almost too old to post to post&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using CloudReady on an off on this laptop for a while now. Everything works pretty swimmingly. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the whole Google ecosystem, then using CloudReady should be pretty seamless.
I&amp;rsquo;ve seen many reviews with agendas, either their own or someone else&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using CloudReady, A Linux/Chromium OS Distro - Part 1 (11/8/2015)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/11/08/using-cloudready-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2015/11/08/using-cloudready-part1/</guid>
      <description>Back to blogging a bit because I&amp;rsquo;m recovering from some surgery. Nothing major. Its only been almost a year and half since my last blogging. :-)
So last time I blogged I used my Toshiba Satellite A105-S4254 laptop to test out Android-x86. A fun experiment, and proved to myself that Android can be used as a desktop if you don&amp;rsquo;t need sophisticated content creation.
Since then I used this laptop to create my own &amp;ldquo;DIY Chromebook&amp;rdquo; using Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChromiumOS on my XPS M1530 (and other computers)</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2013/03/30/chromiumos-on-my-xps-m1530-and-other-computers/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been itching to see how a ChromeOS device works. I want to see how well a ChromeBook would fill the home computing needs. Since I have this nice Dell Latitude XPS M1530, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d do some research to see if I could run ChromeOS on it.
There is a person, Hexxeh, who provides nightly builds of the open source ChromiumOS project. These can be downloaded as bootable USB flash drive image, VMWare or VirtualBox disk images.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>