<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://riotsu.com/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://riotsu.com/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What A Find, Bandcamp.com!</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2011/03/19/bandcamp-more-then-music-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2011 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2011/03/19/bandcamp-more-then-music-store/</guid>
      <description>Surfing can be fun. I am usually targeted in my use of the Internet, but I&amp;rsquo;m really glad I found this website.
It started out from a potentially annoying thing. Someone whom I have no relation, nor do I have any idea why they wanted to &amp;ldquo;be my friend&amp;rdquo; on Last.fm. That site isn&amp;rsquo;t the website of interest, and I love Last.fm to get recommendations on music. Anyways, I found out it was a band that was being &amp;ldquo;sly&amp;rdquo; as also being a &amp;ldquo;user&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thought on Carbon Capture and Storage</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2009/03/11/a-thought-on-carbon-capture-and-storage-and-more-clean-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2009/03/11/a-thought-on-carbon-capture-and-storage-and-more-clean-air/</guid>
      <description>I just read an interesting introduction to &amp;ldquo;Carbon Capture and Storage&amp;rdquo; technology (CCS). Not bad, though I know little. One thing that I think needs a bit more thought is the storage part. They mentioned storage in geological formations deep underground. This speaks of a fundamental part that most people miss. Everything in life is a system. I guess it nice that its underground, far away and &amp;ldquo;not in my backyard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision At The Creation of Ideas</title>
      <link>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/11/22/collision-at-the-creation-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://riotsu.com/blog/2008/11/22/collision-at-the-creation-ideas/</guid>
      <description>I was watching either the Daily Show or the Colbert Report the other night. Well, actually both, but I can&amp;rsquo;t remember which one started this idea. During one of them, the guest made an interesting comment (probably in his book).
It was actually two points about &amp;ldquo;the energy crisis&amp;rdquo;. One was a larger comment about bubbles, and that when they burst, they usually leave something significant behind. And the other was related that a bubble of having 100,000 people try out ideas; with 1,000 of them being worth pursuing and 100 of them being brought to a wider audience to try and perhaps 2 having staying power.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>