<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughtful on (soon to be) riotsu.com</title>
    <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/categories/thoughtful/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughtful on (soon to be) riotsu.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Ralph deGennaro; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 17:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rmdegennaro.github.io/categories/thoughtful/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Perspective on Taking Time to Smell the Roses</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2011/02/26/a-new-perspective-on-taking-time-to-smell-the-roses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2011/02/26/a-new-perspective-on-taking-time-to-smell-the-roses/</guid>
      <description>Talking with Becca this morning, two relevant thoughts merged into one and came out in the conversation. No need to go into details of that conversation; but that bit of the conversation was something I wanted to get &amp;ldquo;down on paper&amp;rdquo; (at least it feels important to do so at this point in time). It is the subject of this post and was good motivation to try to write posts again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The “Ground Zero Mosque” Debate Makes No Sense</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/08/21/ground-zero-mosque-debate-makes-no-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/08/21/ground-zero-mosque-debate-makes-no-sense/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start posting links to articles I like. Word of mouth and discussing things among friends is what helps make the world more cohesive and ultimately a better place. It also helps lessen fear and increases strength within and without.
So my first is this article: 3 Reasons the “Ground Zero Mosque” Debate Makes No Sense
A highlight is that rhetoric should never replace logic. Our lives are not controlled by fear, and fear spreads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Great Individual - Jesse Howes</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/04/18/a-great-individual-jesse-howes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2010/04/18/a-great-individual-jesse-howes/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sad to say that an individual of great strength, warm and perspective has passed on. I knew Jesse from working with Life Is Good and Project Joy, and really only saw him at those times. But I always remembered him and will always remember him as a great person and for the great impact he had on the world. Life Is Good has a post about Jesse Howes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Save The World, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/03/13/how-to-save-the-world-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/03/13/how-to-save-the-world-part-2/</guid>
      <description>After watching the movie &amp;ldquo;The Watchmen&amp;rdquo;, I had an idea. Its sorta related to the movie &amp;ldquo;Hero&amp;rdquo; as well. And can be said of any story that shows people doing extraordinary things to &amp;ldquo;save the world&amp;rdquo;. No matter the context/size of what &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rdquo; means.
From the start I don&amp;rsquo;t want people to think that I don&amp;rsquo;t like those movies. They inspire me to try to get better to do &amp;ldquo;extraordinary&amp;rdquo; things myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thought on Carbon Capture and Storage</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/03/11/a-thought-on-carbon-capture-and-storage-and-more-clean-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/03/11/a-thought-on-carbon-capture-and-storage-and-more-clean-air/</guid>
      <description>I just read an interesting introduction to &amp;ldquo;Carbon Capture and Storage&amp;rdquo; technology (CCS). Not bad, though I know little. One thing that I think needs a bit more thought is the storage part. They mentioned storage in geological formations deep underground. This speaks of a fundamental part that most people miss. Everything in life is a system. I guess it nice that its underground, far away and &amp;ldquo;not in my backyard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Election Results, 2009</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/01/20/election-results-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2009/01/20/election-results-2009/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in a while. And this one isn&amp;rsquo;t really mine. But, like many, for the first time in a long time, I look to the future with a promising smile. Thanks to Jen, Jim and Ken for their wonderful words.
Barak Obama! Freakylicious President! Get your &amp;ldquo;Mo Jo&amp;rdquo; on! A Haiku from Jen Jag
In bare feet by the thousands, chain-yanked off the auction block, In pinched shoes moving on northward flight, In just bought boots down the new hallways of Tuskegee, In spikes churning up the Berlin dirt under the Fuhrer’s eye, In laced-high shoes stepping through the ring to meet Schmeling In ankle high russet browns trudging through the mud of Anzio and stumbling over the crushed rock of Okinawa, In flashing feet breaking for home plate and all of Brooklyn’s approving roar, In the patent leather shoes of three little girls taking guarded steps to school, In wild gliding, unstoppable, sliding motion on the floor of the Apollo, In steel-toed GPs scrambling for cover at Tet and slogging the water-logged Mekong, In stride, linked and determined, on the march, a preacher’s shined shoes at the fore, from Selma to Montgomery, Albany, Birmingham, Chicago, and up the steps to dream in Lincoln’s shadow, that long shadow cast across the generations, across the throngs of Washington Mall who have been on the move from every corner of the country and pause now in wonder at where the weary feet have led.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collision At The Creation of Ideas</title>
      <link>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2008/11/22/collision-at-the-creation-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2008 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rmdegennaro.github.io/blog/2008/11/22/collision-at-the-creation-ideas/</guid>
      <description>I was watching either the Daily Show or the Colbert Report the other night. Well, actually both, but I can&amp;rsquo;t remember which one started this idea. During one of them, the guest made an interesting comment (probably in his book).
It was actually two points about &amp;ldquo;the energy crisis&amp;rdquo;. One was a larger comment about bubbles, and that when they burst, they usually leave something significant behind. And the other was related that a bubble of having 100,000 people try out ideas; with 1,000 of them being worth pursuing and 100 of them being brought to a wider audience to try and perhaps 2 having staying power.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>